hey everyone welcome back to our Channel
I am back with another interesting topic
in the TSA automation
playlist so we are going to talk about
uh error which you might come across
when you are trying to execute a test
keys or you are trying to execute a
execution list or or even a test event
now this could happen for a number of
different reasons it could happen if
you're working uh in your own workspace
or it could happen if you're working on
a multi-user workspace uh in a project
where you have got lots of team members
working on the same project right so uh
let's first talk about what is the Ser
about and then we will talk about uh why
this occurs and how you can resolve this
okay so uh for this I'm going to execute
a particular execution list okay so uh
it's here uh this is the execution list
which I want to execute so looking at
the execution list you don't see
anything wrong here okay so it has
passed once and then it has failed once
and this is the execution list and then
it is under execution folder we have
also got some logs right now uh when I
try to execute this so I try to execute
the execute ution
list okay uh I get error like this okay
so unable to run the selected items no
phys executor was found right um now it
is also giving you a reason here but uh
this is not always the case Okay
sometimes you might just get this line
which is unable to run the selected
items and no phys executor was found now
looking at this error uh it is very
difficult to find out what might be the
issue uh it might look like uh the
executor is having some problem right
especially when you are executing a test
event okay in that case you might think
that it is a error with your distributed
execution or your distributed execution
agent is not working but that is not the
case okay so when you run it in an
execution list you could get the reason
why it is not running so it is very
simple uh it is saying that this
particular test step is not referencing
a module okay now um to debug a little
further okay so if uh we go back to this
particular test case right so if I go
back to this test
case so here uh if I look at this
particular test step right so if you
look at this test step you will see uh
there is no module attribute Associated
which is being shown uh in the test step
right now the values are still intact
but uh the module is showing that it is
not
associated now uh what is the reason
behind this and why did this happen Okay
so if I try to uh jump to this
particular module I don't have any
option and that is because there is no
module which is associated with this
which means the module which was earlier
associated with this particular test
step has been removed uh by mistake or
somebody else has removed that module or
replaced that module or renamed that
module right a lot of things could have
happened and this could happen by
accident or um this could happen for
some reason right we don't know what
that reason could be but that module was
removed from the workspace and once uh
it is removed then uh it will be removed
from uh the test step which it was
associated with now let me show you
another example of how this could happen
Okay so uh we have got this another
execution list which is the swag Labs so
if I go to jump to test case here uh we
have got some standard modules like open
URL and close browser okay uh obviously
you cannot remove these standard mod
modules but there is a module uh which
is user login now this is application
related so if I jump to this
module uh it references this particular
module okay now um by mistake uh if
you're are working in a team and
somebody uh has removed this module okay
so if I go here and if I delete this um
it will also show me a warning that it
is associated or used in one test step
so basically you should not remove it
right but still somebody has maybe
cleaned up some modules or he's working
on something which is not required so he
goes ahead and remove this or this could
be done by mistake as well so once this
is removed now if I go back to the test
case you will see here that it shows me
no module attribute Associated no modu
attribute Associated and for this right
remaining Things Are fine but now if you
go ahead and try to run this so it is
not going to run the complete test case
even though we have CAU some other
modules but uh it will not run this
because one of the module is missing so
that step which is referencing that
module will not work so the test case
itself will stop working
okay so this is um how this particular
error CA is caused okay it comes up uh
frequently especially when you're
working in a multi-user workspace uh and
a multi-user repository where lots of
people are working and uh you are not
following best practices so uh these
kind of things uh do generally happen
but uh we should be aware of why this
error is occurring and then obviously uh
to solve this uh what we need to do is
uh we need to remove this particular uh
test step okay
and then uh we need to um add it back
into this okay so once you remove this
then that particular error will uh not
occur okay so if I run this now it will
not give me any
error so uh let's try and run this
again and you will see that uh it will
open the browser and then uh it will
close the browser so whatever steps are
present it will execute those steps okay
so now the problem uh is resolved right
uh it is able to execute this particular
execution list because we have removed
that particular test step which was
having the problem obviously to fix this
completely you need to rescan or you
need to scan that particular application
and create a module and then uh add your
test step back into this particular test
case so this was all about the error
which comes up uh
pretty frequently which is Executor not
found so uh this is the reason behind
the error uh it is due to a missing
module in your
workspace that's all for this particular
video if you have any questions then
please leave it in the comments if you
like this video then please subscribe to
our Channel thanks for watching and I
will see you in the next video